huzlers.com 2019-12-17

# Privacy Policy

Updated June 8, 2019

Please take a moment to read this Privacy Policy carefully before you use huzlersmedia.mystagingwebsite.com by using our website, you indicate that you accept the Privacy Policy and that you agree to abide by it.

Huzlers policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to [huzlersmedia.mystagingwebsite.com](https://www.huzlers.com/) (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “https://www.huzlers.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the huzlersmedia.mystagingwebsite.com. As a multinational company with primary offices in the United States, we conform our data use to the European Union’s (“EU”) General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), with effect from 25 May 2018.  Therefore, in this Privacy Policy, we would like you to know what kind of personal data we collect from you or that you provide to us, how we process it, on what legal bases, whether we transfer or disclose it, and how long we retain it, in accordance with relevant laws.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Huzlers collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Huzlers purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Huzlers visitors use its website. From time to time, Huzlers may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Huzlers also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on https://www.huzlers.com blog posts. Huzlers only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Huzlers websites choose to interact with Huzlers in ways that require Huzlers to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Huzlers gathers depend on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog to provide a username and email address.

**Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Advertisements**

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Huzlers and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Huzlers may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Huzlers may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Huzlers.com does not disclose your personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

To enrich and perfect your online experience, Huzlers uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising, and store your preferences on your computer.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Huzlers uses cookies to help Huzlers identify and track visitors, their usage of https://www.huzlers.com, and their website access preferences. Huzlers visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Huzlers websites, with the drawback that certain features of Huzlers websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to Huzlers use of cookies.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Huzlers may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Huzlers sole discretion. Huzlers encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users.

https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en  
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.  
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

• Remarketing with Google AdSense  
• Google Display Network Impression Reporting  
• Demographics and Interests Reporting  
• DoubleClick Platform Integration

**Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

**According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our footer menu. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on every page located on the bottom footer.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:  
**•** [On our Privacy Policy Page](https://www.huzlers.com/privacy-policy/)

Can change your personal information:  
**•** By emailing us at admin@huzlersmedia.mystagingwebsite.com

**How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?**

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It’s important to note that we, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

Do we let third-parties, including ad networks or plug-ins collect PII from children under 13.

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify you via email within 1 business day. We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
